CURRICULUM VITAE

21st of October, 2022

Elo Mertanen

student of information technology Laurea University of Applied Sciences

sokrime@outlook.com

Kotikyläntie 7 A 19

02770 Espoo

+358453426553



Summary

Very experienced with customer service and organizing groups of people. I have 10 years of work experience from restaurant field of work as supervisor and as employee. My experiment with working different kinds of people will be very big strength with my next field of work. I'm very energetic and capable of working independently and as in groups.

My curiosity for different kinds of subjects and urge to learn new things everyday are my biggest strengths. I believe that teamwork and good social work environment will be the future of workspaces.

Experience

Kinkerikokit 2012-2019

As a kitchen helper. Preparing dishes and serving customers at weddings, graduation parties etc.

Finnish sauna society 2015-2019

as a café staff and cook. My tasks were serving customers, cooking, cleaning and managing sauna society member accounts.

Work Buddy Oy 2018-2022

as a cook and shift manager. During my shift I was accountable everything what happened during the shift as well as giving orientation for my co-workers. I also took a part for incretions of the new check out system as well as for new websites.

Education

Bachelor of Business Adminitration, Degree programme in Business Information Technology, Laurea University of Applied Sciences, 2022- ongoing

Basics of Information Technology, 1 year period, Haaga-Helia Applied University of Sciences, 2020-2021 Vocational Qualification in Restaurant and Catering Services, competence area in baking, Baker-Confectioner, 2013-2016

Espoo Upper Secondary School for Adults, 2013-2016

Language skills	Finnish	Swedish	English	Japanese
Spoken	First language	Basics	Intermediate	Basics
Written	First language	Basics	Intermediate	Basics

It-skills

	Basics of	html. iava	a. pvthon. d	css. office 365	programs, social	l media platforms	s. blende
--	-----------	------------	--------------	-----------------	------------------	-------------------	-----------

Volunteer work and hobbies

Scout and scout leader 2004-2019

Ropecon 2017, accommodation attendant

Ropecon 2018, Info operative

Ropecon 2019, Info operative

Tracon 2019, accommodation attendant

Ropecon 2022, ticket seller

Tracon 2022, manager of lobby services

Other

Hygiene proficiency certificate 2013

First aid certificate 2015

Attachments

attachment 1

attachment 2

attachment 3

Elo Mertanen